Chibuike Ukandu

Software Developer

<u>+</u>234 9039 9308 86 <u>codexjay08@gmail.com</u>

Linkedin

I am a self-taught frontend developer with expertise in creating responsive websites using industry best practices. As a passionate front-end developer, I constantly strive to grow my technical and soft abilities in order to build software solutions that provide the best possible user experience.

Work Experiences

Front end Developer Intern at Innovation Growth Hub

- Built a clone of Facebook siign up page with HTML and CSS.
- Built a fitness training schedule page with HTML and CSS.

JUN 2020 - AUG 2020

Front end Developer Intern at WeJapa Internships

Built a Gallery page with HTML and CSS

JUN 2020 - SEP 2020

Front end Developer Intern at SideHustle Internship 3.0

- Built an Athlete Application page with HTML and CSS.
- Built a Coming Soon page with HTML and CSS.

SEP 2020 - NOV 2020

Front end Developer Intern at ZURI Internship

- Built a clone of Google Homepage with HTML and CSS.
- Transformed figma designs to responsive web pages with HTML, CSS and Vanilla JavaScript.
- Built an ECare website with HTML and CSS.
- Built my Resume with HTML and CSS.
- Built a Hoarding website with HTML, CSS and Vanilla JavaScript.

MAR 2021 - OCT 2021

Front end Developer Intern at SideHustle Internship 4.0

 Built landing pages with HTML, TailwindCSS and Vanilla JavaScript

SEP 2021 - NOV 2021

Education

GitHub

AltSchool School Of Engineering

Software Engineering 2022 - 2023

Skills Set

Front end development

I design responsive, interactive using various UI tools such as

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, SCSS/SASS, JavaScript, React JS

Tools

Visual Studio Code, GitHub

Languages

• English (Fluent)